# Sina Olfati

## Front-end Developer (React.js)

🔀 sinaolfati6@gmail.com 📞 +989941669736 😲 Kermanshah, Iran 🛗 26/01/2003

https://sina-olfati.github.io/sina-olfati-site in https://www.linkedin.com/in/sina-olfati-872950233

https://github.com/sina-olfati

#### **Profile**

I'm a 19 years old Front-end developer (react). I've invested my youth hours in deep learning to optimize myself to add the most value to your company; Doubt that? Just visit my site, ask my former employers... Or hire me and watch my career for 1 month.

Leave anything you worry about to me; improving your site creatively? Leading a team? Making your work environment more friendly? What are you waiting for?

Skills			
React.js	• • • • •	Next.js	••••
TypeScript	• • • • •	PWA	••••
SPA	• • • • •	Redux	••••
Redux-Thunk	• • • • •	Recoil	••••
Rest API's	• • • • •	Axios	••••
Material UI	• • • • •	Tailwind	• • • • •
Formik	• • • • •	Responsive Design	• • • •
Docker	• • • • •	Git/GitHub	••••
Scrum	• • • • •	JavaScript	••••
CSS	• • • •	HTML	• • • • •

## **Experience**

08/2022 – 11/2022 London, England(UK)

## **JavaScript Developer**

VModel □

- Led the web development team, consisting of 4 members, for 3 weeks; Increased quality and speed by 50%
- Helped the members with coding when they were stuck; Increased speed and teamwork spirit by 40%-60%
- Made unique pages by building user-friendly, interactive and innovative user interfaces; 50% improvement in user experience

Contact: Shinor Spellz - WhatsApp number: +447377919954

05/2022 – 08/2022 Tehran, Iran

#### Front-end Developer (React.js) Intern

Clickhub (Noavaran Dadepardaz click) 🖸

- Learned and applied useful front-end skills; being able to build sites 200% more professionally
- Learned: Redux Redux-Thunk, TypeScript, PWA, Material UI, Formik, Docker, Scrum, PSD to HTML & CSS

Contact: Nima Bakhshi - WhatsApp & Telegram Number: +989363806000

### Languages

EnglishPersian (Farsi)Kurdish"Perfect" grade diplomaNativeNative

#### **Portfolio**

#### Sina's Site 🛮

• Technologies: React.js, TypeScript, PWA (It is installable), Material Ui, SPA, Formik, i18next (made it multilingual), JavaScript, CSS, HTML

### Sina's Shop 🛮

• Technologies: React, Redux, Redux-Thunk, TypeScript, PWA, SPA, JavaScript, CSS, HTML

#### **Education**

08/2021 – present Bachelor's of Teaching Experimental Science

Tabriz, Iran Allameh Amini University 🖸

2018 "Perfect" grade English language diploma

Qasr-e Shirin, Iran Padideh Academy of Foreign Languages

2016 Honorary diploma in mathematics

Kangaroo International Olympiad ☑